ACTWU's Out-of-Business Contracts 5619/035
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Mann Industries. Dow Badische. Local 1526. [folder 1 of 2], 1961-1983 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Mann Industries. Dow Badische. Local 1526. [folder 2 of 2], 1983-1993 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Manufacture Finnie. Local 2502., 1989-1995 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Marblehead Lime. Local 1695T., 1992-1995 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  Thornton, IL
- Mario Casuals. Local 25/63., 1982-1993 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Marlenn. Local 2513., 1990-1994 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Baltimore, MD
- Mechanic Towel Supply. Local 331., 1975-1978 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Melton Shirt. Local 345., 1976-1996 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Batavia, NY
- Mid-Hudson Legal Services. Local 2557., 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  Poughkeepsie, NY
- Moire. Phoenix Moire. Local 1733., 1952-1993 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  Fairlawn, NJ
- J. Molofsky and Sons. Local 51/70., 1960-1993 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Monsport. Local 2499., 1986-1995 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  French. Iberville, Quebec, Canada
- Mr. T's Apparel. Local 779C., 1993-1996 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  Crystal Springs, MS
- Napp Chemicals. Local 7587., 1949-1995 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  Lodi, NJ
- National Knitting Mills. Dylex Diversified. Local 1865., 1972-1989 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Native Textiles. Local 1824., 1970-1997 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  Dallas, PA
- New Center Clinic East. Local 365., 1992-1995 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- New Modern Wet Wash. Local 332., 1975-1978 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  Flushing, NY
- Northern Feather. Local 696T., 1946-1992 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  Newark, NJ
- Nu-Tex. Local 1602., 1965-1993 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  Dunellen, NJ
- Oggi. Local 2584., 1992-1998 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Old Stenton Sponging. Local 352., 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Private Line Group. Kuppenheimer/Dadeville Manufacturing. Local 2569., 1991-1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Dadeville, AL
- F. E. Plankenhorn Braid Works. Penn Garment. Local 1914., 1976-1994 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Old Lycoming, PA
- Pacific Columbia Mills. Local 254., 1991-1996 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Columbia, SC
- Pagano Gloves. Local 1486., 1969-1996 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Johnstown, NY
- Paragon Dyeing and Finishing. Local 1733. [folder 1 of 2], 1946-1987 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Paragon Dyeing and Finishing. Local 1733. [folder 2 of 2], 1988-1993 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Park Hall., 1973-1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  Montreal, Quebec, Canada
- Perfect Outerwear. Local 178., 1969-1993 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Perstorp Components. Local 2474., 1991-1997 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  Fort Wayne, IN
- M. S. Pietrafesa. Local 240., 1993-1997 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  Carrollton, GA
- M. S. Pietrafesa. Local 243., 1993-1997 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  Sturgis, KY
- Pike Manufacturing. Local 2574., 1991-1994 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  Troy, AL
- Pine Shirt. Local 136C., 1976-1995 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  Pottsville, PA
- Polo Coat and Apron Supply. Local 331., 1975-1978 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  Middle Village, NY
- Polyfelt Americas. Local 2606., 1993-1996 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  Evergreen, AL
- Polytex. Local 2052., 1961-1991 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  Bayonne, NJ
- Posture Mattress. Local 124., 1993-1996 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  Shelbytownship, MI
- Prince Gardener. Local 179., 1991-1994 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  Searcy, AR
- Principal Clothing., 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Private Brands. Local 335., 1993-1995 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Progressive Uniforms. Local 170., 1969-1990 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Pyramid Outerwear. Local 178., 1966-1993 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Quick Roll Leaf. Peacock Roll Leaf. Local 1790., 1961-1994 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  Elmhurst, NY
- Rangeley Clothes. Local 158., 1977-1993 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- R. C. Textile Printing. Local 1790 [folder 1 of 2], 1947-1986 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- R. C. Textile Printing. Local 1790 [folder 2 of 2], 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Reb Plastics. Local 1806., 1969-1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Avon Lake, OH
- Regent Manufacturing. Local 1932., 1964-1993 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Passaic, NJ
- Rite Sole. Local 205A., 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Wright City, MO
- R-Gee Originals. Local 170., 1966-1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Hatboro, PA
- Riteway Laundry. Local 332., 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Rockelman Appliance Service. Local 1748., 1965-1995 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Royal Palace. Local 124., 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Royal Shirt., 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Concord, Ontario, Canada
- Rubens Royal Uniform. Local 231., 1980-1985 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Russell Uniforms. Local 162., 1974-1985 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Sackville Mills. Local 178T., 1941-1991 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  Wallingford, PA
- Salaison Acton. Local 2329., 1994-1999 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  French. Acton Vale, Quebec, Canada
- Sandess Manufacturing. Local 1243., 1977-1995 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Scali Taylors. Local 162., 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Scarcelle Clothing. Local 75., 1977-1990 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Schuylkill River Industries. Local 33T., 1964-1992 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Shiff and Company. Local 858/274., 1972-1994 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Shifren-Willens. Local 364., 1966-1995 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  Oak Park, MI
- Signode Packaging. Local 6., 1976-1992 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Soldick Fabrics. Local 7587., 1974-1995 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Solomon. Local 640., 1959-1984 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Leeds, AL
- Somerset Cleaners. Local 124., 1993-1996 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  Troy, MI
- Springs Industries. Local 2608., 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Nashville, TN
- Steiner. Local 915C., 1992-1995 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  Ogden, UT
- Sterling Dye. Local 33T., 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Steven Salen. Local 162., 1980-1985 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Stratford of Puerto Rico. Local 2556., 1990-1993 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Ciales, PR
- Studio Reproductions. Local 1790., 1955-1993 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Sun Clothes. Local 170., 1969-1994 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Sunset Hat and Cap. Local 2H., 1990-1993 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Superior Knicker. Local 4., 1977-1985 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  Jersey City, NJ
- Susan Shoe Industries. Local 314SW., 1981-1991 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  Stoney Creek, Ontario, Canada
- Sweetheart Laundry. Local 332., 1975-1978 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- F. R. Tripler and Company. Local 400., 1969-1985 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Tesser Textile. Local 252., 1951-1994 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  North Bayshore, NY
- Textile Monterey. Local 1686., 1967-1997 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  French. St. Jean, Quebec, Canada
- Thomson. Local 2609., 1993-1997 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  Thomson, GA
- Tobin-Hamilton. Local 280., 1989-1995 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  Mansfield, MO
- Toxey Apparel. Local 1145., 1992-1995 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  Toxey, AL
- Trench Manufacturing. Local 49., 1970-1996 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Tri-Con. Local 2626., 1995-1998 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  Cape Girardeau, MO
- Troy Shirtmakers Guild., 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  Glens Falls, NY
- TRW. Devor Metal Products. Local 1698., 1968-1993 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- U. S. Tailoring. Local 177., 1978-1995 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Unitex Knitwear. Local 7587., 1980-1993 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- C. N. Vicary. HSSI Distribution. Local 2519., 1988-1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  Columbus, OH
- Ve-Alite Plastic. Local 1790., 1963-1993 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Velourit. Local 2052., 1946-1986 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  Hoboken, NJ
- Walker International. Local 365., 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Wallachs. Field Brothers. Local 340., 1966-1987 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Weavexx. Local 2324., 1978-1994 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  Arnoprior, Ontario, Canada
- Wellington Home Products. Local 7587., 1953-1995 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Wells Lamont. Portland Glove. Local 122G., 1960-1994 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  Carlton, OR
- Welsh Company. Local 2516., 1987-1993 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  Gordonville, TN
- White Plans Coat and Apron. Local 300., 1975-1978 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  Peekskill, NY
- Winthrop Laundry. Local 331., 1975-1978 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Xerox, Versatec. Local 1414J., 1990-1993 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  Santa Clara, CA
- Xerox. Local 14T., 1983-1989 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  Monrovia, CA
- Yocum Knitting. Local 1148., 1950-1994 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  Stowe, PA
- Youngs Cleaners. Local 124., 1993-1996 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  Farmington, MI
- Zwicker Knitting. Local 741C. [folder 1 of 2], 1958-1982 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  Appleton, WI
- Zwicker Knitting. Local 741C. [folder 2 of 2], 1983-1993 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Zwicker Knitting. Eagle Knitting Mills. Local 1567., 1962-1993 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Shawano, WI
- Dry Cleaners Labor Relations Group. Local 124., 1973-1996 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Chase Packaging. Local 402T., 1992-1997 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Portland, OR
- Chester Clothes. Local 1099., 1994-1998 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  Philipsburg, PA
- Davis Clothing. Local 1., 1977-1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Brockton, MA
- Dehen Knitting. Local 901., 1978-1996 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Global Clothing. R & M Kaufmann. Local 529., 1995-1997 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Essex Manufacturing. Local 177., 1942-1999 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Allen Morrison. Local 1624., 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  Lynchburg, VA
- Angelica Textile Services. Local 800., 1993-1998 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  Milford, CT
- Bemis Company. Local 606., 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  Memphis, TN
- Canstar Sports Group. Local 308SW., 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  Cambridge, Ontario, Canada
- Carleton Woolen Mills. Local 2313., 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  Gardener, ME
- Flexel. Local 1470. [folder 1 of 3], 1959-1970 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  Covington, IN
- Flexel. Local 1470. [folder 2 of 3], 1970-1989 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Flexel. Local 1470. [folder 3 of 3], 1983-1996 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Hutch Sports USA. Local 200C., 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  Erlanger, KY
- Illinois Public Action Fund. Local 2458., 1984-1997 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Jay Garment. Local 295C. [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1986 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  Portland, IN
- Jay Garment. Local 295C. [folder 2 of 2], 1986-1999 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Louis. Local 177/335, 1977-1998 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  Boston, MA
- Louisville Manufacturing. Local 2560., 1992-1998 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  Louisville, KY
- Manchester Knitted Fashions. Local 359/2427., 1960-1999 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  Manchester, NH
- Pawnee Pants Manufacturing. Local 137., 1965-1996 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Olyphant, PA
- Pendleton Woolen Mills. Local 291/265., 1961-1996 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Pillowtex. Local 317T., 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  Eden, NC
- Presglas. Local 1811., 1972-1996 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  Greenfield, IN
- Richmark International., 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  Everett, MA
- Jomac. Local 33T. [folder 1 of 2], 1947-1978 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Jomac. Local 33T. [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1990 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- J. Schoeneman. Local 717C/719/718., 1956-1998 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Standard-Keil Hardware. Local 328/279., 1976-1999 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  Allenwood, NJ
- Stanwood Mills. Local 730B., 1988-2000 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  Slatington, PA
- Levi Strauss. Local 915., 1995-1997 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  Albuquerque, NM
- Suzy Shier., 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Tennessee Woolen Mills. Local 2466., 1984-1997 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  Lebanon, TN
- Tuxedo Junction. Local 210C., 1996 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  Hamilton, Ontario, Canada
- Velva Sheen Manufacturing. Local 2308. [folder 1 of 2], 1977-1993 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Velva Sheen Manufacturing. Local 2308. [folder 2 of 2], 1993-1998 (Box 20, Folder 6)